Gather round, come take a look...
It's time for Theatre of Darkness.
Can I choose?
This is the story of a woman who was heading home on the last train.
Service for today has ended. Thank you very much for riding with us.
Are you waiting for your mom or dad?
Do you live nearby?
I see...
Then, do you want to walk back with me?
Do you have any siblings?
Did something happen at home?
Did you get into a fight with your mom?
Sorry for asking so many questions you don't want to answer.
Is this your home?
Yeah.
That room on the first floor.
Actually, I don't want to go back.!
I hate mom.
Did your mom do something to you?
i don't want it.
That's a problem.
What should we do in a time like this?
Hey, can I choose?
Choose? Choose what?
Can I choose you to be my new mom?
Can I choose?
That's...
What is it?
You're being noisy.
I'm sorry,
I brought your child back...
I don't have any children.
But there was a little boy at the station...
Ah!
Isn't it here?
You know...
Certainly,
Just a moment ago, there was a child...
What you're saying makes no sense,
so please leave.
Bye.
Huh?
Ma'am?
So you do have children after all?
Can you hear them too?
Yes.
Ugh, why are they still so loud even after dying?!
Um... Maybe you should go check on your children...
Why did things turn out like this?!
Huh?
What is all this?!
Just leave, go home!
Three months later,
I found out I was pregnant.
My husband was overjoyed with our first child.
but I couldn't get that boy from that night out of my head...
That boy's words...
Mommy!
As he grew up,
my child began to look more and more like the boy from that night.
Mommy, hurry!
Deep down,
I felt a strange uneasiness,
and I couldn't fully love this child.
Taku-chan.
What's wrong?
This is...
that apartment from that night.
Everyone is still here, you know.
Huh?
They're the babies who died before they could learn how to speak.
That's why all they could do back then was cry.
Taku-chan, you...
They're watching us.
Watching?
See? They're all jealous of me.
Because I was the one who got to become your child, Mommy.
Let's go home, hurry!
Hey... can I choose?
Can I choose someone to be my baby brother or sister?
Can I choose?
The end